Guide to the John N. Paden papers, 1938-2010
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
- Series 2: Research, 1950s-2007; (81 boxes)
  - Nigeria recent developments, September 25, 1978-1980s (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Nigeria resources, 1980s (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Nigeria trip, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Nigeria trip, Carter delegation, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Nigeria trip, receipts, 1999 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Nigeria various, 1960s (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Nigeria various, 1970s (Box 56, Folder 10)
    Includes article and personal correspondence from Jean Herskovitz, information on Nigerian economy.
  - Nigeria various, 1980s (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Nigeria various, December 1995 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Nigerian Anthropological and Sociological Conference, December 17-21, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    Folder 1 of 7.
  - Nigerian Anthropological and Sociological Conference, December 17-21, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    Folder 2 of 7.
  - Nigerian Anthropological and Sociological Conference, December 17-21, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    Folder 3 of 7.
  - Nigerian Anthropological and Sociological Conference, December 17-21, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    Folder 4 of 7.
  - Nigerian Anthropological and Sociological Conference, December 17-21, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    Folder 5 of 7.
  - Nigerian Anthropological and Sociological Conference, December 17-21, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    Folder 6 of 7.
  - Nigerian Anthropological and Sociological Conference, December 17-21, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    Folder 7 of 7.
  - Nigerian conference, 1960s (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Nigerian conference, May 5, 1999 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Nigerian Development Commission, 1995 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Nigerian economy, September 10, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Nigerian elections, clippings, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Nigerian presidential election, February 1999 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Nigerian news, March-May 1965 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    Includes articles on women's issues.
  - Nigerian politics, 1960-1965 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Nigerian politics, 1966-1967 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Nigerian politics, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Nigerian politics, January 28, 1996-May 1996 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Nigerian politics, 1998-1999 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Nigerian politics and economics, 1970s-1980s (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Nigerian strife, 1960s (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Nigerian strife-Biafra, 1967-1969 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Nigerian unrest, 1960s (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Nigerian unrest, 1960s (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Nigeria's future, March 6, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Niyass, Ibrahim and other, 1963-1964 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Northern Nigeria, 1909-1954 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    Includes information from the Northern Nigeria Marketing Board.
  - Northern Nigeria Ad Hoc Conference, Nigeria Constitution, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Northern Nigeria Ad Hoc Conference, Northern views, 1966 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Northern Nigeria, background information and sources, 1906, 1951-1963 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Northern Nigeria, background information and sources, 1962-1966 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Northern Nigeria, background information and sources, 1955-1967 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Northern Nigeria, biography, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Northern Nigeria census, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Northern Nigeria geography/demography, 1960s (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Northern Nigeria history, 1911 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Northern Nigeria history, 1960s (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Northern Nigeria legal, 1950s-1960s (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Northern Nigeria modernization, 1964 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    Newspaper clippings.
  - Northern Nigeria politics and development, 1962-1965 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Northern Nigeria sources, 1926-1962 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Northern Nigeria various, 1901-1957 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Northern Nigeria various, 1957-1963 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Northern Nigeria various, 1963-1965 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Northern Nigeria various, undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Northwestern, 1980s (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Northwestern, 1980s (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Northwestern, 1980s (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Northwestern African Studies, 1972 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Northwestern African Studies, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Northwestern African Studies, 1980s (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Northwestern papers and events, 1980s (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Northwestern political science, 1980s (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Northwestern various, 1976-1980 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Northwestern various, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Northwestern various, 1982-1985 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Northwestern visitor information, 1970-March 1971 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - ORSP copy-PAS/Hausa, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Oil in Nigeria, Africa, 2005-2009 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Oklampo, 1967-1970 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Optima, 1970 1971 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Optima, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Other writings, "early" marked on original folder, undated (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Otite, Onigu, July 1972 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Outline, undated (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Oxford, 1960s (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Oyediran, Oleyeye, January 13, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Oyediran, Oleyeye, January 13, 1979 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - PAS, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - PAS Workshop follow-up, January 1981 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - PAS Midwest directors, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - PAS people/reception list, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - PAS Program, October 1981 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - PAS restructuring and priorities, 1971-1972 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Pada, Lansine, March-December 1979 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Paden, Dr. John N., 1965-1970 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Paden, John N. Dissertation, February 1968 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Palmer, H.R. Sources, 1928-July 1929 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Parliamentary debates, May 4, 1960-February 25, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Part I. Intro. The Kano Religious Legacy, undated (Box 66, Folder 4)
    (7) marked on original folder.
  - Peace Corps, Ann Paden, 1960s (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Peace Corps training manuals, 1960s (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Peacemaking and conflict resolution, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Permanent mission of Nigeria, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Photocopies of article, booklet, undated (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Plants and medicines, 1960s (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Political, 1963-1965 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Political, 1990s (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Political integration, undated (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Politics, 1980s (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Politics, Biafra and bombings, 1960s-1970s (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Politics, development issues, 1998-2008 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Politics of African states, 1960s-1970s (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Presentation on Belgium and Switzerland, 1978-1981 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Pre-Fulani Islam in Northern Nigeria, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Pregnancy and birth, Ann Paden, 1960s (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Presidential elections-Carter Center, 1999 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Proceedings-African Studies and International Programs, January 1981 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - "Project" marked on original folder, 1986 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - "Project-Clipping" marked on original folder, August 22 and 24, 1983 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Public administration training schools, undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Ann Paden, 1960s (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Pulaphilly Book: Islam, January 27, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Racial Solidarity Among Black Troops, March 12, 1973 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Radcliffe, Ann Paden, 1964-1967 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Radcliffe, Peter, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Rapporteur's notes, February 25, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Receipt, Washington trip, June 1980 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Religion and Political Culture in Kano, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    Folder 1 of 6.
  - Religion and Political Culture in Kano, 1971 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    Folder 2 of 6.
  - Religion and Political Culture in Kano, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    Folder 3 of 6.
  - Religion and Political Culture in Kano, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    Folder 4 of 6.
  - Religion and Political Culture in Kano, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    Folder 5 of 6.
  - Religion and Political Culture in Kano, 1971 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    Folder 6 of 6.
  - Religious biographies, undated (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Religious Tolerance, October 3-5, 1991-December 7, 1994 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Report of the Constituency Delimitation Commission, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Resettlement, Federal Capital territory, January 30, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Resettlement survey, September 1980 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Ronen, Dov. Harvard seminars, November 21, 1979-Spring 1980 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Rubenstein, Albert H., May 1, 1973 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Rufai, Aisha, 1982-1983 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Rural Africana research notes, Winter 1968 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - SOAS Conference, April 1980 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Sanders, Jim, 1999 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Sanusi, Ado, July-September 1964 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Savannah Centre, November 6, 1995 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Scarritt College: African Summer Program, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Seminar, Amir Al-Muminin Muhammad Bello, April 15-18, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Seminar, Amir Al-Muminin Muhammad Bello, April 15-18, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Seminar, Amir Al-Muminin Muhammad Bello, April 15-18, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Seminar, Amir Al-Muminin Muhammad Bello, April 15-18, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Seminar, Amir Al-Muminin Muhammad Bello, April 15-18, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Seminar, Amir Al-Muminin Muhammad Bello, April 15-18, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Sheridan, 1979-1980 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Smallpox, Ann Paden, April-May 1965 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Smythe, Dr. Mabel Murphy, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Sokoto, 1978-1980 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Sokoto Training College, notes, undated (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Special seminar, medical practice, April 20-23, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Stamps, undated (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Stewart, Charles "ASA", May 17, 1968 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    Contains extensive materials related to African studies and a small amount of correspondence with Charles Stewart.
  - Structure of Central Authority, undated (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Succession to leadership, clippings, 1954-1964 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Sufism, undated (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - "Summer: Legal/Mary", Summer 1982 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Survey technique, Ann Paden, 1960s (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Tapiero, Grand Sheik, undated (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Teaching About Africa seminar series, 1986 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    Folder also contains one sheet of 12 slides for use with the seminar.
  - Theology, other, 1960s (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Theory of Emirate State, 1932-1965 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - "Thesis ideas", 1960s (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - "Thesis outline", 1960s (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - "Thesis, Part IV, JNP", undated (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - "Thesis outlines, outdated", 1960s (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Tijaniyya development, October 1964-February 1965 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    Includes information on Ibrahim Niasse.
  - Tijaniyya functions, 1960s (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Tijaniyya functions, 1960s (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - To do lists, September-October 1971 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - To do lists, January 1980 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Travel related documents, 1980s (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Tukur, Mahmoud-presentation, April 20, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Tukur, Mahmoud-review, April 1999 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Types of medical practitioners, Ann Paden, 1960s (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - US/China African studies, November 14, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - US/Nigeria Policy Conference, March 11, 1999 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - US/West Africa, 1970s (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Ubah, Kano emirate in 19th Century, May 1976 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified author, African Revolutionary, 1980s (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified author, Biography: Sa'idu Ben Hayatu, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Unidentified author, intended for Ann Paden, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified author, Life History of M. Sa'idu Ben Hayatu, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified coup d'etat manuscript, undated (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Unidentified coup d'etat manuscript, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - United Nations, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - University of London, conference, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - University of Sokoto, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - University of Sokoto folder, undated (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Usumaniyya, 1962, 1965 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Uvulectomy, Ann Paden, 1960s (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Values and social science, September 19-20, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Various, 1960s (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Various, 1962-1963 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Various, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Various, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Various, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Various, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Various, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Various, 1970s (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Various, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Various, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Various, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Various, 1980s (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Various, 1980 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Various, 1981 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Various, 1982 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Various, 1983 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Various, 1984 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Various, 1990s (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Various, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Various, 1993-1994 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Various, 1995 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Various, 1996 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Various, 1999 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Various, 2000s (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Various, undated (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Various-Ann Paden, 1960s (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Various conference papers, 1967-1968 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Various conference papers, 1970s (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - Various conference papers, 1970s (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Various conference papers, 1970s (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Various conference papers, 1970s (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Various conference papers, 2004-2007 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Various index cards, culture: women, children, medical. Ann Paden, 1960s-1970s (Box 80)
  - Various index cards, culture: women, children, medical. Ann Paden, 1960s-1970s (Box 81)
  - Various index cards, 1960s-1970s (Box 82)
  - Various index cards, 1960s-1970s (Box 83)
  - Various notes, 1960s-1970s (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Various sources, reprints, 1855-1963 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Various sources, reprints, 1960s (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Vikmani, Akbar and Caroline Bledsoe, Spring 1987 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Visit to Kumasi of W. Huydecoper, undated (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Vocabulary lists, undated (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Voice of America, March 11, 1981 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - WMRT, 1970s (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - WMRT, 1970s (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Wall, Christopher. NUP Publishing, July 28-October 25, 1978 (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - West Africa, culture, 1950s-1960s (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - West African Chiefs Conference, December 16-19, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - West African Chiefs Conference, December 16-19, 1968 (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - West African language survey, 22586 (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - West African Political Science Conference, March 4-6, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - "What is a theory?", undated (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Wilkes, Ivor, July 1969 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Wisconsin, December 12, 1995 (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Women's issues, Ann Paden, 1960s (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Workshop on African Studies and International Programs, January 16-17, 1981 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - World System, 1970s (Box 85, Folder 7)
- Series 3: Publications, 1959-2010; (37.5 boxes)
  Includes books, journals, newspapers, catalogs from publishing houses, and various ephemera. Contents relate mainly to Nigeria, but also included are items relating to other African nations as well as to the US and UK. Collection includes more than twenty different newspapers which were published in Nigeria, but primarily written in English. Organized by subject and then chronologically.
  - Africa Digest, August 1981-February 1963 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Africa Publications, 1961-1962 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Africa Report, 1968-October 1971 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Africa Special Report, October 1959-October 1961 (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - African Peace Review, October 1997 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - African Quarterly, 1960s (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - African Review, May 1965 (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - African Spark, October 1974 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - African Studies, April 1957-1959 (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - African Studies Review, 1982 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    Volume XXV, Numbers 2/3.
  - African Studies Review, 1982, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    Volume 26, Numbers 3/4, Volume 27, Number 1.
  - African Urban Notes, March-December 1967 (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - African Urban Notes, June-December 1968 (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - African Urban Notes, February-May 1968 (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - African Urban Notes, March, Summer, Winter 1970 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - African Urban Notes, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Agenda, September 1980-December 1981 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Ahmadu Bello University, 1972-1973 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Arabic language books, undated (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Bayero University, Kano, 1979-1980 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Bohannan, Paul, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - CTEC, 1977-1978 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Commission of Enquiry Reports, 1960s (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Commission of Enquiry Reports, 1968-1696 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Democracy, 1999 (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Department of State, July 23, 1973 (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Eacrotanal, 1980s (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Education, September 1981 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - "egghead" Ahmadu Bello University Fine Art Department, 1963, 1964 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - English as a foreign language, 1979-1981 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Eric M. Bonner company catalogs, 1960, 1962-1963 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Ghana, 1961-1971 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Hague, 1960-1962 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Harvard, "Unofficial Guide to Graduate life", 1961-1962 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - Haske-the light of Islam, September 1968-February 1969 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - Hausa language publications, 1950s (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Hausa language publications, 1950s-1960s (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Historical Society of Nigeria, December 1956-December 1963 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Institute for Social Research: A Guide to Research and Services, 1972-1973 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Institute for Social Research: A Guide to Research and Services, 1973-1974 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - International Educational, Cultural and Related Activities, August 1961 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Islam, February, December 1980 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Jiagge Commission Report, 1964 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Jiagge Commission Report, 1964 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Journal of African History, 1968, 1971 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    Volume IX, Number 2, Volume XII, Number 1.
  - Journal of African History, 1974 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    Volume XV, Numbers 1, 2.
  - Journal of African History, 1974, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    Volume XV, Number 4, Volume XVI, Number 2.
  - Journal of Modern African Studies, May 1972, December 1977 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Kano periodicals, 1968-1974 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Kano State, 1970s (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Kellogg, 1985-1987 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Krauss periodicals, undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Law & Disorder: The Chicago Convention and its Aftermath, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Mahawara, April 6-May 3, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Muryar Damagaram, September 1, 1965-December 21, 1967 (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Muryar Damagaram, January 4, 1968-May 28, 1970 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Niblock, Tim and Richard Lawless, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Nigeria, government and politics, 1960s-1990s (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Nigeria trade journals, 1963, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - Nigeria yearbook, 1985 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - Nigerian Administration Research Project, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Nigerian book publishers, 1960s (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - Nigerian politics and development, 1960s-1970s (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - Northern Nigeria, 1960s (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Northwestern, 1979-1980s (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - Northwestern, 1984-1985 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - P.A.S., 1982, 1983, 1985 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - P.A.S. Field Museum, 1973-1974 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Palmer, H. R., 1931 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    The Carthaginian Voyage to West Africa in 500 B.C. together with Sultan Mohammed Bello's Account of the Origin of the Fulbe.
  - Political, 1990s (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Popular culture, 1970s (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Second National Development Plan, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Southern Africa, South Africa, September 1967-December, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Travel, California, 1970s (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Travel, California, 1970s (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Travel, Chicago, 1970s (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Travel, Chicago, 1970s (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Travel, Czechoslovakia, 1963, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Travel, Illinois, 1970s (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Travel, Illinois, 1970s (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Travel, Michigan, 1970s (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Travel, Minnesota, 1970s (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Travel, New Mexico, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Travel, Other, 1970s (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Travel, Other, 1970s (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Travel, Texas, 1970s (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Travel, Wisconsin, 1970s (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - UN: Structure and growth of African economies, 1958 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - US government pamphlets on Africa, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - US government pamphlets on Africa, 1968 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - University of California, 1970-1971 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - University of Sokoto, 1978-1979 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - University of Sussex, 1967-1970 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - University of Texas at Austin, 1970-1971 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Various, 1959 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Various, 1960-1961 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Various, 1963, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Various, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Various, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Various, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Various, 1970 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Various, 1971 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Various, 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Various, 1975-1976, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Various, 1980-1982 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Various, 1985-1986, 1987 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Various, undated (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Various, academic, 1955-1969 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Various, academic, 1977-1981, undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Various, catalogs, 1960s (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Various, catalogs, 1962-1966 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Various, catalogs, 1967-1969, undated (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Various, catalogs, 1970s (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Various, catalogs, 1969-1970 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Various, catalogs, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Various, catalogs, 1970-1971 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Various, catalogs, 1971 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Various, catalogs, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Various, catalogs, 1971-1972 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Various, catalogs, 1980s (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Various, catalogs, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Various, catalogs, 1980-1981 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Various, catalogs, 1990s (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Various, catalogs, undated (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Various, periodicals, 1960s (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Various, periodicals, 1970s (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Various, periodicals, 1980-1981 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Various, periodicals, 1997-1999 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Various, periodicals, 1999 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Various, periodicals, 2007 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - West Africa, 1960s-1970s (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - West Africa, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - West Africa, 1980s (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Abuja Inquirer, December 24, 2009-January 10, 2010 (Box 111)
  - Business Day, December 22, 2006-January 7, 2008 (Box 111)
  - Daily Champion, February 26, 1999-April 23, 2007 (Box 111)
  - Daily Independent, April 20, 2007-January 26, 2010 (Box 111)
  - Daily Sketch, April 13, 1979-February 28, 1999 (Box 111)
  - Daily Sun, December 20, 2006-May 20, 2007 (Box 111)
  - Gaskiya, July 2, 1965-March 23, 1970 (Box 112)